抱歉我来晚了
Oh, my late arrivals.
欢迎来到地球上最美妙的地方
Welcome to the best place on earth--
昔日
The past.
上缴你们所有现代物品的时间到了
Time to turn in all modern-day devices.
噢  妈呀
Oh, dear.
呃...
Um...
你所说的“现代”到底是什么意思呢
So exactly how like "modern" are we talking?
因为我的手机已经挺老了
'cause, I mean, my phone's pretty old.
我想我大概是六个月前买的吧
I think i've had it for at least like six months.
可是拓荒者们没有手机  你也不能有
Well, if the pioneers didn't have it, neither can you.
哦对了  别忘了上缴你们的梳子
Oh, and don't forget your hairbrushes.
我们是拓荒者  又不是动物
We're pioneers, not animals.
开疆时代的妇女们会自己削多余的柴禾
On the frontier women would whittle hair-grooming tools
来制造梳头工具
Made out of leftover firewood.
梳子拿好不谢
Here's a comb.
我的宝贝们啊
My babies.
别担心  亲爱的
Don't worry, sugar.
每个人都是有值钱玩意的
Everyone has their price.
嘿 我用“老妈架子圣诞节”的签名照
How about I trade you that curling iron
换你的卷发棒怎么样
For a signed copy of "a very butt bomb christmas"?
哦 丽芙 我们要谈谈
Oh, liv, honey. we should talk.
我开始怀疑你是不是因为我没邀请你而不高兴了
I'm starting to wonder if you're upset that I didn't invite you.
你怎么可能会这么想呢
Why ever would you think that?
你从国家的另外一边
You brought in a substitute mom
带来了个冒牌妈妈
From the other side of the country.
这不是个明显的信号么
It's kind of a red flag.
哦  也许你是对的  妈妈
Oh, yeah, maybe you're right, mom.
也许我确实有点不高兴
Maybe I am a little bit upset.
也许我现在要在你的比赛里打败你了
Maybe now I will beat you at your own game.
引用拓荒者们的话就是
As the pioneers would say,
愿君祥瑞
I bid you good day.
这改变不了什么
This changes nothing!